Hello everyone, today I'm going to show you how to make a non-woven fabric.
The non-woven fabric makes it hard to see the seam line on the fabric.
And the seam line will be more even when you press the fabric together.
First, use a sewing machine to sew all the seams on the fabric.
Then, change the strength of the sewing machine to 0 on the right.
Then, change the tool to adjust the seam line.
As you can see, there is no seam line on the fabric.
Next, I'm going to show you how to press the fabric together.
I'm going to use a sewing machine.
You can add the seam line and the seam line to make the seam line.
Choose the seam line on both sides of the fabric and open the seam line.
The width of the seam line is 6.
You can choose the type of the seam line according to the effect.
If the seam line is too thick, the seam line won't fit.
Then on the two-line seam line.
On the right, find the inner seam line.
Here I set the inner seam line with a seam line of 6mm.
As you can see, this is the seam line.
Set the center of the filling line on the right.
It is the same.
Adjust it, turn on the direct rendering, and then we click on the blank area to choose to open the control key to open the simulation.
You can take a look at the effect.
You can see that now we have the effect of this pressure glue in the gap.
The effect of this gap is done.
So we have the same way of making this sleeve.
Let's do it quickly.
Next, let's hide the platform and let's see the position of the gap.
The difference between the gap is that it will have a gap here.
In the same way, let's do the effect of this gap in the gap of the upper part.
Notice that we didn't select the extension bar here, otherwise it will extend to the bottom edge of our board.
Similarly, we also need to cancel the selection of the internal line and extend the internal line.
The position of the gap.
Our.
The width will be different.
Here we set it to 12 mm.
Next, let's make the lower board.
The lower board and the bottom board of the sleeve are the same way of making.
Here we can change the width of our bar according to the need.
Note that the width of our internal line and the width of our bar are the same.
It's a little bit different.
The width of the thanks are the same and the height of the bottom is equal.
Now, you can see the seam allowance on one side of ourisparent is done.
Then the other side is also the same method of making.
Now we have finished the making of the chest and sleeve.
Finally, let's take a look at the neck.
First, the same as before, we now make a seam allowance,
On the collar, you can find a string, the width and the size of the shirt.
Then on our large body collar, we are going to select all the two outer threads of the seam allowance.
And we go to the back of the collar.
Here, we can only talk about the settings.
We can only talk about the settings.
Now it's time to received the shape.
And you can see the pages down below our big body collar,
are facing outwards.
So if we point in straight, they'd have 30 percents greater than 180 percents.
The angle here is 240 percents.
And on the side, we can see the next line.
If it's not too obvious here, we can adjust the intensity of this part
Make it a little bigger
Now our costume is done
Thanks for watching!